Shrek the Halls is a adventure, animation, comedy
film directed by Gary Trousdale.
The Christmas tree isn't the only thing green in this new holiday classic.
Shrek is back and trying to get into the spirit of the season.
After promising Fiona and the kids a Christmas they'll remember, he
is forced to take a crash course in the holiday.
But just when he thinks he has everything for their quiet family
Christmas just right, there is a knock at the door.
Shrek (voice), played by Mike Myers.
Donkey (voice), played by Eddie Murphy.
Princess Fiona (voice), played by Cameron Diaz.
Puss in Boots (voice), played by Antonio Banderas.
Pinocchio / Three Pigs (voice), played by Cody Cameron.
Gingerbread Man (voice), played by Conrad Vernon.
Shrek the Halls is an American animated Christmas comedy television special that
premiered on the American television network ABC on November 28, 2007.
The thirty minute Christmas special was co-written and directed by
Gary Trousdale and produced by DreamWorks Animation.
Mike Myers, Eddie Murphy, Cameron Diaz, and Antonio Banderas
reprise their roles from the feature films.
This Christmas special takes place after the events of Shrek the Third.
It grossed $16 million in home sales.
The title is derived from the title of the Christmas carol, Deck the Halls.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
cat, holiday, fairy tale, cartoon.
The tone is lighthearted.